(Howard:)And I'm gonna miss you, too.
(Raj:)I just want you to know,
(Raj:)I'm happy to look in on Bernadette
while you're gone.
(Howard:)Thank you.
(Raj:)And if anything were to happen
to you,
(Raj:)we will name our
firstborn son Howard.
(Raj:)I'm just kidding.
(Raj:)We'll name him Dalib,
after my grandfather.
(Penny:)This one looks nice.
(Leonard:)No. Sheldon doesn't like
reclaimed wood.
(Penny:)Why not?
(Leonard:)He's afraid the original owners
will come back.
(Penny:)Well, Sheldon's not here.
(Leonard:)Well, he is here.
(Leonard:)Unless you want to dig him out
with a bone saw and a melon baller,
(Leonard:)there's nothing I can do about it.
(Penny:)All right, sweetie,
you're paying for this table,
(Penny:)and it's your apartment, too.
(Leonard:)-I know, but--
-No buts.
(Penny:)You got to stop
letting him boss you around.
(Leonard:)You're right. I mean,
he decides what TV shows we watch,
(Leonard:)what food we eat,
who my favourite hobbit is.
(Leonard:)I wanted Frodo,
but we can't both have Frodo,
(Leonard:)so guess who's stuck
with Samwise Gamgee.
(Penny:)See? Right there.
You're a grown man,